http://www.knittinghelp.com/about/website-policy

Free Shipping on Interchangeable Needle Kits in our Shop!
Check out the Updated KnittingHelp.com iPhone App!
Web Site Policy
Outer Limits Media, Inc. d.b.a KnittingHelp.com. ("KnittingHelp.com," "we," "us") shares your concerns regarding the protection of your personal information online. This Privacy & Security Policy ("Policy") describes our practices regarding the collection and use of information through our website, located at www.knittinghelp.com any of our sub sites and any web pages (collectively, the "Site"). By using the Site or obtaining any product or service through this Site, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Site.
We may from time to time update this Policy. You can determine when this Policy was last updated by checking the "Effective Date of Current Policy"  found at the bottom of the Policy.
What Information We CollectKnittingHelp.com collects the following types of information during your visits to our Site.
First, we collect non-personally identifiable information. When visitors come to our Site, we collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages of the Site were visited, the order in which they were visited and which links were "clicked." Collecting such information involves logging the IP addresses, operating system and browser software used by each visitor to the Site. Although such information is not personally identifiable, it may be possible to determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of the visitor's point of connectivity.
We use "cookies" to collect non-personally identifiable information regarding you. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. Cookies make it possible for us to recognize your browser when you visit our Site. By doing this, we can personalize your return visits and save you time during login and checkout. Your browser must be set to accept cookies in order for you to enjoy the benefits of being a registered user of the Site.
We collect personal and personally identifiable information such as your name and email address when you sign up to be member of our forum. Additionally, if you purchase products through our store we request additional personal information such as your address and billing information in order to process your order.
How We Use Collected InformationPlease take some time to familiarize yourself with the different ways that KnittingHelp.com uses the information that we gather. Keep in mind that, while we encourage all third parties (Merchant America, PayPal, Google, etc.) involved in running our business to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our visitors and to otherwise handle personally identifiable information in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received either from KnittingHelp.com or independently.
Non-personally Identifiable InformationKnittingHelp.com uses non-personally identifiable information, such as your IP address and the pages that you visit on our Site, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Site and improve Site-related services and features. Your IP address and other non-personally identifiable information also may be used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and Site usage trends. This information aids us in advertising and in developing the Site.
We also may share aggregated statistical data and other non-personally identifiable information with our current and potential business partners, and with our service providers. Such information includes the total number of visitors in a particular month or the top keyword searches that landed people on the Site. We will never disclose personally indentifiable information to third parties unless requires by a law enforcement agency.
Personally Identifiable InformationKnittingHelp.com uses personally identifiable information collected from you to:
complete transactions initiated by you such as the sale and delivery of products from our store
provide support services for products or forum issues
get in touch with you when necessary
contact you to make sure you are satisfied with our products and web site and to find out how we can serve you better
conduct in-depth marketing research
verify access to access-restricted services such as our store, forum or blogs
We do not sell, rent, or offer personally indentifiable information collected from you to other companies or individuals. Financial information (credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, billing address, and so forth) is used to bill you for products purchased through our store. You may, from time to time, receive information from us regarding new features, new products and special offers we think you'll find valuable.
KnittingHelp.com also may use your personally identifiable information to "pre-populate" forms that are used by the Site to facilitate transactions with us. Other types of use by us of personally identifiable information are discussed below.
Children and ParentsChildren under the age of 14 are permitted to register for membership on KnittingHelp.com but must seek the permission of a parent or guardian beforehand. Parents or guardians may request that their child's account be removed from KnittingHelp.com at anytime. Information collected during registration is only used to complete the registration and process and facilitate the functions of the forum. Personal information is never shared with 3rd parties or released to other members.
Service ProvidersWe work with third parties (Merchant America, PayPal, etc.) who provide services, including but not limited to order processing and fulfillment, credit card clearance and other services of an administrative nature. Personally identifiable information may be shared with such third parties for the purpose of providing such services.
Third Party WebsitesThroughout our web site you will find links to other sites, including sites that may or may not be owned or operated by KnittingHelp.com. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. If you visit such websites, we encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of the sites.
How Your Information Is Stored
KnittingHelp seeks to use reasonable security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information that is under our control. To protect your personal information all account and checkout pages of our store are encrypted using 256-bit encryption provided by GeoTrust. We do not store or otherwise save credit card information. Once your order has been placed your credit card information is removed from our records.
General account information such as name and address information are stored within a database on our servers. The server is protected behind and firewall and the database is only accessible from local connections originating from our local area network.
Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of the foregoing, while we seek to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and KnittingHelp.com's servers, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the Site. You provide all such information at your own risk.
How To Update Your Personal Information If you have signed up for an account with KnittingHelp.com, you may update your mailing address, email address, name changes, forum details, or billing information by accessing you either your Store Account or your Forum Account, where you can sign into your account to review and update your personal information.
KnittingHelp.com Forums, Chat and BlogsThis Site may make chat rooms, forums and/or blogs available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Contacting KnittingHelp.com
If you have any questions about this Policy, the data collection and usage practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact:
KnittingHelp.com
P.O. Box 3306
Amherst, MA 01004-3306
Effective Date of Current Policy: October 30th, 2008
Jump to more videos...
